So you see other people within your
profession getting online clients,
which means they can work from wherever
they want, whether maybe in a
fancy cafe or even a remote place like
Bali.
So you think to yourself,
you want a piece of the action.
You're not quite sure where exactly you
need to start to make that happen.
Now, one of the biggest mistakes
that I made back in the day
was thinking to
attract online clients,
I needed a really fancy website, and I was
wrong. And in the next few minutes,
I'm going to save you probably $3,000 to
$9,000
that some dodgy bastard
was going to charge you online for a
flipping
website.
There are three main predicaments we're
going to face.
Number one, if we don't need a website,
where is it we send people?
Number two, what is a landing page
and how should we approach it?
Number three,
if we do send someone to a landing page
and not a website, how can
we make sure that people buy?
So let's look at number one.
We need a page that's created with one
purpose and one purpose only,
to make sales.
Unfortunately,
the majority of websites online have so
many different sections and
places to click. About me, contact,
services, products.
Not to mention, some people try
and get your email address with a pop-up
and it's
all a bit overwhelming.
Do you want my email?
Do you want my business?
Am I reading about the fact you used to
swim for county?
And before you know it, poof,
they're gone and they're not going to
return.
There are many pieces of software out
there, but my favorite is Leadpages.
This isn't a sponsored video, which
is actually one of my gripes.
Why trust someone who's paid to promote
something?
I've never been paid by Leadpages,
and I've sent nearly 1,000 coaches there,
because to me, it's the best.
And you're probably wondering why.
Well, simply because Leadpages,
and probably other competitors to it,
can give
us analytics on how many people
are visiting and how many of those people
visiting
were converted into sales.
And it also gives us the ability to A/B
split
pages. This means
that we can make multiple versions of the
same page, and it
will split our traffic to the different
pages and see which one performs best so
we
can double down on it. Whether it's video,
more text, less text, more video,
shorter video, whatever it is.
And it also means we can determine whether
or not we
have a traffic problem
or a conversion problem.
Because if we're getting loads of visitors
and no sales, that's a conversion
problem.
If we're getting good conversion
percentages, but there's a poor number of
people visiting in the first place,
we have a traffic problem.
Imagine your landing page being like the
fact you're an owner of an Italian
restaurant in the Amalfi Coast
and people are walking by.
Now,
you know they're wanting somewhere to eat.
7:00 PM. It's evening.
They're looking at the menu.
If they'd eaten,
they wouldn't be looking at the menu.
And it's not your job to go there
and hard sell them to get them to sit down
and
book in a 45-minute call to see whether
or not they're a good fit for your
business. It's to simply present a menu.
"Hey,
this is what we do." You might have a fish
restaurant where you specialize in
fish. You might have a meat restaurant,
and if you've got a meat restaurant,
you're
not worried about what vegans think
looking at your menu.
It's your job, "Hey, this is what we have.
Take a look." If it's expensive
and they can't afford it,
that's fair enough.
But no Michelin-star restaurant
is out there trying to do deals with
people that
can't afford their food.
They just cater to a different audience.
And once they have the menu,
you give them a few minutes.
If they have any questions they can ask.
But the idea is that your menu answers all
the questions for them, so you don't
have to spend all your time doing it.
As a restaurant owner,
you can't be too pushy. You can't,
"Please come in here.
Please come in and have dinner in our
restaurant." But on the other hand,
you can't
be too nonchalant that you don't care.
You still have to be proactive
and go up to the people that
are looking for a place
to eat. And if they're not interested,
let them go,
because they will remember the
interaction they had with you outside the
restaurant, and if they don't find
anything better, they will come back.
That's why we don't want to be too pushy.
Your landing page serves the exact same
purpose.
And then number three,
we need to ensure we have a good flow.
What it is, why they need it,
what they get, why they should trust you,
and how to
buy.
And a good header video does great things
as well. Be honest.
This morning I was helping someone in my
mentorship called Jayden.
He's only 17,
and I scripted this to be the header video
for his page.
"Hey, I'm Jayden. Yes, I'm young. Yes,
I'm baby-faced.
Yes, I just finished college. And yes,
I live at home with my mom.
Yes, I don't have that much life advice,
but I'm good at this and I want to show
you how. Because of my situation
and baby face, I don't
charge much at all.
But as you've probably seen online in my
profile, I really care
about helping people.
And one day I'm going to have two things.
One, a beard, and two,
a much higher charge than I
charge for coaching. So whilst you can,
why not put your trust in me, hire me as a
coach, and see how good I really am?
And if at any point in the first month,
fuck it, two months, you
don't think I'm the best coach you've ever
used, I'll refund you in full.
How's that? Right, my prices are below.
Speak soon.
Thanks for watching." How many people
are going to be able to listen to a spiel
like that and not feel compelled to buy?
Although that doesn't fit the flow of what
it is, what they get, you can just come
out and be honest with people.
They just want to be disarmed.
They don't want to be conned.
They want to feel comfortable.
So with that in mind,
you should be all really excited to go
and build a landing
page, and you can send traffic to it
and wake up with the money in the bank.
But if you're left wondering how you can
get hundreds of people to visit your
landing page in just the click of a
button,
then you're going to need to understand
the ins and outs of why it's not just a
good idea, but imperative that you
operate an email list.
And you can find out everything you need
to on
that by clicking this video right here.
I appreciate you watching.